[{"answer": " Thank you, kind sir", "docId": "Happy-Birthday_-Wanda-June.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "A what kind of doctor", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": " You're going out", "docId": "Happy-Birthday_-Wanda-June.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Take plenty of cigars", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "He'd kill me.  He'd be right to kill me, to", "docId": "Happy-Birthday_-Wanda-June.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "He'd assume we had", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "I know", "docId": "Happy-Birthday_-Wanda-June.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "I don't want to go to that place", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "That's when I'll get my confidence back", "docId": "Happy-Birthday_-Wanda-June.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "If you'll pardon the expression, that's when you'll see the fur and feathers fly.  Good night", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "I see", "docId": "Happy-Birthday_-Wanda-June.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Good night", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": " This is very good for us", "docId": "Happy-Birthday_-Wanda-June.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "The wilder my friend is tonight, the calmer he'll be tomorrow", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "We've got to find him.  I want you to show me exactly where you saw him last.  And you stay here, my friend, in case he comes home.  That's all he sai", "docId": "Happy-Birthday_-Wanda-June.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "What was it", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "We tried to be.  We tried to be", "docId": "Happy-Birthday_-Wanda-June.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Dead!  Such a final word.  Dead!  Did you hear that", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "We'll miss you so", "docId": "Happy-Birthday_-Wanda-June.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Oh, oh, o", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Hm", "docId": "Happy-Birthday_-Wanda-June.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": " A bitch", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "At least", "docId": "Happy-Birthday_-Wanda-June.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "It's enough that you've brought yourself home", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "It's enough that you've brought yourself home", "docId": "Happy-Birthday_-Wanda-June.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": " Tell them yourself", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "I think so, daughter.  How old are you", "docId": "Happy-Birthday_-Wanda-June.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "A springbok, an oryx, a gemsbo", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "As a matter of fac", "docId": "Happy-Birthday_-Wanda-June.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": " Hello", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "The Germans shot everybody who lived there, then leveled it, plowed it, planted turnips and cabbages in the fertile ground. They wished revenge for the slaying of the Beast of that place.  To their twisted way of thinking, your father had butchered an Eagle Scout.  Play lots of contact sports", "docId": "Happy-Birthday_-Wanda-June.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "You're supposed to get hurt", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Thank you, my friend.  You're a wonderful man.  You really are. Everybody respects you for what you've done for scouting and the Little League", "docId": "Happy-Birthday_-Wanda-June.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "I'm saying n", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Tough luck.  You'll have to split the fee", "docId": "Happy-Birthday_-Wanda-June.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "She's crying because she's so happy", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "I didn't get his name.  A friend of your father", "docId": "Happy-Birthday_-Wanda-June.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "He isn't", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "He isn't any friend of Father", "docId": "Happy-Birthday_-Wanda-June.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "He is my father", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "None", "docId": "Happy-Birthday_-Wanda-June.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": " Good night", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "Wants to fix up her makeup, no doubt", "docId": "Happy-Birthday_-Wanda-June.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Alive and hale.  He's throwing a little surprise party for his own family.  Is your mother often this unstable?  my friend", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": " What are his symptoms", "docId": "Happy-Birthday_-Wanda-June.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "What does he say to do", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": " Well no", "docId": "Happy-Birthday_-Wanda-June.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "You've been bitten by bats", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "More and more we find ourselves laying aside false pride and looking into the pharmacopoeias of primitive people.  Curare, ephedrin", "docId": "Happy-Birthday_-Wanda-June.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "That's an editorial we, of course. I haven't turned up anything personally", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "Awful.  I can't tell you how sorry I am", "docId": "Happy-Birthday_-Wanda-June.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": " Do say hello to your mother", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "A hundred dollars", "docId": "Happy-Birthday_-Wanda-June.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "Can I get dressed first", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "No", "docId": "Happy-Birthday_-Wanda-June.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": " I'm not about to introduce to you a jungle novelty.  What I have in mind is massag", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": " Such as?..", "docId": "Happy-Birthday_-Wanda-June.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "Tell me about its sexual roots", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "Yes", "docId": "Happy-Birthday_-Wanda-June.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": " His most cherished possession?  His violin, I guess", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": "I don't think so", "docId": "Happy-Birthday_-Wanda-June.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": " What are you going to do", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": "We only have two members so far, but it's growing all the time", "docId": "Happy-Birthday_-Wanda-June.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": "my friend plays shuffleboard", "qsentId": 64}, {"answer": "We have enough for a shuffleboard team.  In Heaven, shuffleboard is everything.  my friend plays shuffleboard", "docId": "Happy-Birthday_-Wanda-June.txt", "asentId": 67, "question": "my friend plays shuffleboard", "qsentId": 66}, {"answer": "my friend plays shuffleboard", "docId": "Happy-Birthday_-Wanda-June.txt", "asentId": 69, "question": "my friend, who wrote my friend in Wonderland, plays shuffleboard", "qsentId": 68}, {"answer": "my friend plays shuffleboard", "docId": "Happy-Birthday_-Wanda-June.txt", "asentId": 71, "question": "my friend the Ripper plays shuffleboard", "qsentId": 70}, {"answer": "my friend, who wrote my friend in Wonderland, plays shuffleboard", "docId": "Happy-Birthday_-Wanda-June.txt", "asentId": 73, "question": "my friend, who gave us Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs, plays shuffleboard.  Jesus Christ plays shuffleboard", "qsentId": 72}, {"answer": "Of course!  Not only go to it but go to it in full uniform!  Rent a uniform", "docId": "Happy-Birthday_-Wanda-June.txt", "asentId": 75, "question": "Wear your uniform and every decoration, and let them despise you, if they dare", "qsentId": 74}, {"answer": " Hello", "docId": "Happy-Birthday_-Wanda-June.txt", "asentId": 77, "question": "Is my friend in", "qsentId": 76}, {"answer": "How are you, honeybunch", "docId": "Happy-Birthday_-Wanda-June.txt", "asentId": 79, "question": "The posies are for her", "qsentId": 78}, {"answer": "You're free to go to her, if you want.  If you'd rather be a woman and run with the women, just say the word", "docId": "Happy-Birthday_-Wanda-June.txt", "asentId": 81, "question": "I'd rather go to Viet Nam", "qsentId": 80}, {"answer": "I'd rather go to Viet Nam", "docId": "Happy-Birthday_-Wanda-June.txt", "asentId": 83, "question": "What you say is,", "qsentId": 82}, {"answer": "Would somebody please pass me the catsup", "docId": "Happy-Birthday_-Wanda-June.txt", "asentId": 85, "question": "Pass the fucking catsup", "qsentId": 84}, {"answer": "You're an imbecile", "docId": "Happy-Birthday_-Wanda-June.txt", "asentId": 87, "question": "Everybody thinks that", "qsentId": 86}, {"answer": "I feel mocked, insulted, with no sort of satisfaction in prospect. We don't have to fight with steel. I can fight with words.  I'm not an inarticulate ape, you know, who grabs a rock for want of a vocabulary.  Call him up in that place, my friend.  Tell him to come here", "docId": "Happy-Birthday_-Wanda-June.txt", "asentId": 89, "question": " No", "qsentId": 88}, {"answer": "I'll put it in my friend's room, where it belongs", "docId": "Happy-Birthday_-Wanda-June.txt", "asentId": 91, "question": "For what it's worth now, my friend, the clown, gives his sacred word", "qsentId": 90}]